link2gov.com 2009-06-16

# Privacy Policy

Link2Gov Privacy Policy

**INTRODUCTION  
**Link2Gov, Inc. ("Link2Gov") has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy issues. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for Link2Gov. At Link2Gov, we are very committed to your privacy. This is our PRIVACY PROMISE TO YOU: Link2Gov will never sell, exchange, or release any of your individual personal information to a third party without your expressed permission.

**INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT  
**Like other websites, your IP number is visible to us when you visit our website. What is an IP address, you may ask? It is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're connected to the Internet. Your IP number is visible to most of the websites that you visit. Don't worry, though, at Link2Gov, we only use IP numbers to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our website. Other sites may use your IP number for marketing purposes. We don't.

**COOKIES**  
Like many sites, Link2Gov uses cookies. Cookies are data files that are stored on your computer. They contain identification information that enables us to see how our users are interacting with our site and how frequently they are returning. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. We use cookies for the benefit of our users. Cookies let us know if we have repeat visitors (a strong indication of happy consumers) and if we are delivering a quality product to our consumers. We also use cookies to identify which sites our repeat visitors are coming from, so that we can place more of our online advertising on these sites. Essentially, it is an anonymous way to survey how we are doing and to look for other consumers who we think will like our site. If you do not want to accept cookies from Link2Gov or other sites, your browser software should allow you to not accept cookies. Look in the Preferences (Netscape) or Internet Options (Microsoft Internet Explorer) feature to do this.

**CONTACTING Link2Gov  
**If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with Link2Gov, please contact:  
Privacy Policy Issues  
Link2Gov, Inc.  
One Burton Hills Blvd., Suite 300  
Nashville, TN 37215
